# REZA KIANI M.

C/C++ DEVELOPER

#### **ABOUT**

TEHRAN / READY TO RELOCATE

RKM7232@GMAIL.COM

in IN/REZA KIANI ☑

# C/C++ DEVELOPER

#### **ADVANCED**

CPP11 QT5

EMBEDDED DEVELOPER

## **INTERMEDIATE**

EMBEDDED SYSTEMS
ROBOTICS
EAGLE CAD
RASPBERRY PI
ARM MICROCONTROLLERS
(STM32FX)

VOIP BACKEND DEVELOPER

# **ADVANCED BEGINNER**

FREESWITCH OPENSIPS LUA

# OTHER SKILLS

# **ADVANCED BEGINNER**

CPP14, CPP17
OPENCV
VUEJS / JAVASCRIPT
ANDROID / JAVA
GOLANG
PYTHON
GIT

#### LANGUAGES

PERSIAN (NATIVE SPEAKER)
ENGLISH (INTERMEDIATE - B1)

#### **SUMMARY**

I'm a 29 years old C/C++ developer interested in embedded systems, microcontrollers, and electronics, with some experience in the VOIP industry. I also worked on financial-related projects. I am passionate about programming and very flexible in investigating new roles. I prioritize user feedback first, and also I try to moderate the project deadlines.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

TOSAN <sup>□</sup>

04/2021 - PRESENT

C/C++ DEVELOPER

Tosan is a company with products focused on banking solutions. The range of products is from core banking services to ATM and POS software

- Worked with Cpp11, Qt5, Python
- Worked with financial protocols such as Iso8583, Wosa XFS
- Encryption algorithms like RSA, ECDH, ...

# ARYA SAMANEH <sup>☑</sup>

04/2018 - 03/2021

C/C++ DEVELOPER, VOIP BACKEND DEVELOPER

Arya Samaneh is a company with more than a decade of experience in VOIP telecommunication. Also, the company has a multi-platform application that end-users can message or call each other.

- Worked with Cpp11, Cpp14, Qt5 for client application
- PHP7, Lua for backend with Debian9 OS
- Also worked with PostgreSQL, MongoDB as the database for the system
- Opensips, Freeswitch for handling VOIP calls.

# ACOAFRA <sup>☑</sup>

09/2016 - 01/2019

EMBEDDED DEVELOPER

Acoafra is a product design company that it's focus is on digital and electronic instruments based on customer request.

- Worked with C for STM32(ARM), AVR(AtMega), PIC 8bit microcontrollers
- Used protocols such as UART, I2C, SPI, Wi-Fi
- Vuejs for the control panel on PC to communicate with the board
- Also worked with Android (Java) for the android client app.

## MERSA EMBEDDED DEVELOPER

09/2017 - 03/2018

Mersa is a product design company. They consult customers to make their products cheaper during manufacturing

- Worked with C for STM32(ARM), AVR(AtMega) microcontrollers and ESP8266 WIFI chip
- Also worked with Raspberry Pi 3 on a project to play 1080p movies
- Worked with Android (Java) for android application
- Used Wi-Fi, Bluetooth, GPS, GSM modules in multiple projects.
- Using Eagle CAD to design PCB boards

### ARIO ENGINEERING GROUP

09/2014 - 09/2016

EMBEDDED DEVELOPER

Ario was a group made with Robotics students in university to participate in Robotics competitions.

- Designed a flight controller for a UAV robot with a AtMega2560 microcontroller
- Using EagleCAD to design its PCB

# **EDUCATION**

#### SHAHROUD UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

09/2012 - 06/2017

# REFERENCES



We currently are working together at Tosan company. In my opinion, Reza is a passionate and motivated developer. He always tries to do his tasks in the best way and on time. He has good knowledge of programming languages especially C/C++ and also has a good technical level here in this company as a developer. More importantly, he is a fast learner and would like to learn new skills from other colleagues. Moreover, if a person needs any help at work, he is ready to contribute to others to resolve their problems. Reza is amazing and this is not only my opinion, other colleagues have the same opinion as me.

- BEHNAM ARAZKHANI, SENIOR C/C++ DEVELOPER AT TOSAN